http://www.dvdo.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), DVDO, Inc. (“DVDO” or the “Company”) describes its practices with regard to information collected on its websites (the “Sites”). At our Sites, visitors may learn about DVDO, its subsidiaries and its products.
By visiting our Sites or using any of our services, you agree that your information, including your personal information, will be handled as described in this Policy, which is incorporated by reference into our Terms of Use.
What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?
We collect information directly from you, including personal information (collectively, “information” unless necessary to distinguish between personal information and other information), directly from you and through our service provider ChallengePost. We also collect information about your use of our Site through cookies, Google Analytics and other tracking software (please see our section below entitled “Cookies and Other Tracking” for additional information).
We request information from you, such as name and contact information, if you seek additional information about our services or products from the website.
Use of Your Information
We use the information that we collect about you for the following purposes:
To provide our services and products to you, to communicate with you about your use of our services and for other customer service purposes
To better understand how users access and use our Site and services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis
To improve our Site and our services
In accordance with applicable law, for marketing and advertising purposes, such as to notify you (via email or other means) about our special offers and promotions.
Sharing Your Information
DVDO may share your information with the persons/entities below and for the following purposes. DVDO does not share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes.
DVDO Subsidiaries. If you are seeking information from one of our subsidiaries (e.g., MHL, LLC, HDMI, LLC) then we will share your contact information and information about your submission (e.g., name, and contact information) with that subsidiary.
Our Third Party Marketing Vendors. We share the information that we collect about you from our Sites to assist us in providing our services. These vendors may assist us in our marketing efforts, but it does not use your personal information to market its own products and services to you. It may use your aggregate information as discussed below.
Service Providers. Subject to local law, we may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf. For example, these providers may help us administer our Sites.
We also may share your information for the following reasons:
Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the acquiring company.
In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process, such as in response to a subpoena.
To Protect Ourselves and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We use cookies, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs, and similar technologies to track user activity and collect Site data. We may combine this data with the personal information we have collected from you.
Cookies. Cookies allow a web server to transfer data to a computer for recordkeeping and other purposes. We use “cookies” on our Sites to, among other things, better serve you with tailored information and facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Sites. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent cookies. Using cookies, we collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, referring URL, referring website, page views, and your downloads.
Session Cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged in to the Site.
Persistent cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about your activity, which we may combine with other information about you.
Third Party Cookies. We use third parties, such as Google analytics, to track and analyse movement throughout our Sites.
Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer you can edit your browser options to block them in future. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Sites who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Sites.
Special Note For Residents of Germany: please contact us if you do not want us to combine your personal information with information we automatically collect about you.
Local Storage Objects
We may use Flash Local Storage Objects (“Flash LSOs”) to store your Site preferences, to personalize your visit or to display content based upon what you view on our Sites. Flash LSOs are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored. In addition, you cannot control, delete or disable the acceptance of Flash LSOs through your browser. For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash cookies, go to the Adobe Flash Player Help Page, choose “Global Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions. To see the Flash LSOs currently on your computer, choose “Website Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions to review and, if you choose, to delete any specific Flash LSO.
Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Technologies
We use web beacons, such as clear GIFs, web bugs or pixel tags, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs in connection with our Sites to, among other things, track the activities of website visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about website usage. We and our third party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, measure the success of our marketing campaigns, identify when our e-mails are viewed and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.
Do Not Track. DVDO, Inc. currently does not recognize Do Not Track signals. In this section, however, we discuss how you affirmatively may disable certain types of tracking technologies. You also may opt-out of certain advertising from us as discussed below.
Third Party Advertising
Google Ads. Where permitted by law, including for U.S.-based Site visitors, we use Google advertising services to advertise our website, products and services on third party sites. For example, we use Google AdWords to display ads within Google Search results. We also use Google advertising services to display ads about our products, services and website on other third party sites, including for retargeting and remarketing to you about products and services you may have viewed on our website.
Google’s advertising systems may use other technologies, including cookies, Flash and HTML5, to display ads. Google uses cookies and other technologies to collect your IP address, location information and other device information (e.g., device model and browser type), as well as information about the websites you visit, products you view and your Google search words, to determine what ads to display to you.
Other Ad Networks. We also may use other third parties to assist us in advertising our services on third party sites as well as to evaluate the success of our advertising. You may opt-out of many third-party ad networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”). For more information regarding this practice by NAI members and DAA members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to opt-out of third-party ad networks operated by NAI and DAA members, please visit their respective websites: www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp and www.aboutads.info/choices.
Third-Party Links
At times, our Sites may contain links to third party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but, instead, is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites, and we are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions, including, where appropriate, password protection, encryption, and SSL to protect our Sites and the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time.
You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, computer, and web-enabled devices, among other things, by signing off after using a shared computer, inserting a password on your web-enabled device, choosing a password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your password private. You should never share your log-in information with others. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen or compromised passwords, or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.
Can I Access and Modify My Personal Information?
If you submitted your information on our Site, you may update your information by emailing webmaster@dvdo.com. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may continue to reside in our systems for a period of time.
What Choices Do I Have?
From time to time, and with your consent to extent required by applicable law, we may send you emails offering products and services that we believe might be of interest to you. If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving these emails, please follow the opt-out instructions contained in any such e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests, and that your opt-out pertains only to the receipt of marketing and advertising promotions and not for issues related to your service.
Terms of Use
Your use of our Sites, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use including applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Terms of Use
Consent to Transfer Information to the United States
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using our Sites and services, you consent to the transfer and processing of your information in the United States, which does not have data protection laws that provide the same level of protection that exists in countries in the European Economic Area. As a result of the transfer, your information may be subject to access by law enforcement and other government entities, including courts and tribunals in accordance with laws applicable in those jurisdictions. Your consent is voluntary. If, however, you do not consent, then we may not be able to provide you with our Services.
Children Under 13
Our Site is not designed for persons under 13.
Changes to this Policy
We may change this Policy from time to time, so be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to our policy to our Sites. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavour to provide you with notice in advance of such change, by highlighting the change on the Sites or by sending an email to you at the email address that you have registered with us.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us at: webmaster@dvdo.com
Sign-up for exclusive news and product updates.
